<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>00-00-00</title>
    <link>https://00-00-00.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 00-00-00</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 21:59:04 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://00-00-00.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Local Minecraft Server on the Internet</title>
      <link>https://00-00-00.github.io/posts/set_up_mc_server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 21:59:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://00-00-00.github.io/posts/set_up_mc_server/</guid>
      <description>I recently got back into minecraft because of a friend. Me being interested mostly in redstone contraptions never got into multiplayer before. Since minecraft is pretty laid back, I thought it would be a great place to hangout with my friend. Whatever may be your reason to play minecraft, when you want to play with another person somewhere else, you start running into a few issues.
I had a free trial month for Realms available to me, so we started our game there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangalore - Leh - Srinagar - Delhi</title>
      <link>https://00-00-00.github.io/travel-diary/ladakh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 22:01:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://00-00-00.github.io/travel-diary/ladakh/</guid>
      <description>The mountains are calling The moment I completed the Bhutan trip, I knew Leh was the next destination. After a failed previous attempt to make it the holy lands of an Indian motorcyclist, I was loosely aware of the destination that I wanted to reach. This time around I knew going in that I am going to be attempting this journey alone, so if it fails it&amp;rsquo;s all on me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Architecture Sandbox #3</title>
      <link>https://00-00-00.github.io/posts/android-arch-part3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 19:38:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://00-00-00.github.io/posts/android-arch-part3/</guid>
      <description>So the task is to set up a Repository that&amp;rsquo;ll interface between the database and the REST APIs. The Repository would have a LocalStore implementation that&amp;rsquo;ll take care of handling the database CRUD, and a CloudStore implementation to take care of the RESTful APIs. We need an implementation of the Repository that&amp;rsquo;ll handle switching between these two interfaces. Since we want an interface and all interactions with the module would be uniform, we need to decide on how the communication would take place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://00-00-00.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 14:40:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://00-00-00.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Arjun here. I am very interested in observing and building systems, be it software systems or a motorcycle engine. Spinning a spanner is one of the most satisfactory feelings, so is when modules interact seamlessly with each other. I&amp;rsquo;ve mostly worked on Android codebases. I am learning about design patterns for software architecture, Restful APIs, databases and website development.
I like really long cross country motorcycle tours. They say that one who travels is the one who learns the most.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangalore - Bhutan</title>
      <link>https://00-00-00.github.io/travel-diary/bhutan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 11:56:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://00-00-00.github.io/travel-diary/bhutan/</guid>
      <description>The Plans I don&amp;rsquo;t clearly remember how the plan started. I can&amp;rsquo;t see how such a plan could have come into our minds except as a joke. I don&amp;rsquo;t think any of us had the faintest clue that we were capable of a such an adventure.
Wanting to see the Himalayas is something that had been driving me to plan for a tour for a long time. We might have picked Bhutan for multiple reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Architecture Sandbox #2</title>
      <link>https://00-00-00.github.io/posts/android-arch-part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 21:22:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://00-00-00.github.io/posts/android-arch-part2/</guid>
      <description>The objective is to write an android application that will fetch some data over the network, store it locally and display the data in a list-detail format.
Since we want to try avoiding couping. We will try adopting the Observer Patter i.e. we&amp;rsquo;ll have modules that emit events and other modules react to to the event. We can use RxJava for a publish-subscribe mechanism. Since we are using RxJava on Android, RxAndroid which provides us nifty Schedulers for managing the threads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Architecture Sandbox #1</title>
      <link>https://00-00-00.github.io/posts/android-arch-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 11:14:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://00-00-00.github.io/posts/android-arch-part1/</guid>
      <description>Around May of last year Android introduced a bunch of new classes around organising code better. Till then Android team never really took a stand to tell the community how to organise their codebases. What I observed was activities started developing unwieldy View classes (Activities and Fragments) that did everything from spawning new threads, making network calls, performing disk writes to anything and everything you could require the application to do.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>