<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel-diaries on 00-00-00</title>
    <link>https://00-00-00.github.io/travel-diary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel-diaries on 00-00-00</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 21:31:10 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://00-00-00.github.io/travel-diary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chandigargh - Shimla - Spiti Valley - Manali - Delhi</title>
      <link>https://00-00-00.github.io/travel-diary/spiti-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 21:31:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://00-00-00.github.io/travel-diary/spiti-valley/</guid>
      <description>After Leh, there were a few choices that were in my bucket list. I was caught between a tour of the northeastern states or the Spiti Valley. In the end, I ended up choosing Spiti mostly because the charm of Spiti is it&amp;rsquo;s not fully discovered by the general populace, unlike Ladakh. Although not fully discovered it is in the process of becoming another Ladakh. Hotels are popping up, the roads will get paved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangalore - Leh - Srinagar - Delhi</title>
      <link>https://00-00-00.github.io/travel-diary/ladakh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 22:01:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://00-00-00.github.io/travel-diary/ladakh/</guid>
      <description>The mountains are calling The moment I completed the Bhutan trip, I knew Leh was the next destination. After a failed previous attempt to make it the holy lands of an Indian motorcyclist, I was loosely aware of the destination that I wanted to reach. This time around I knew going in that I am going to be attempting this journey alone, so if it fails it&amp;rsquo;s all on me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangalore - Bhutan</title>
      <link>https://00-00-00.github.io/travel-diary/bhutan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 11:56:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://00-00-00.github.io/travel-diary/bhutan/</guid>
      <description>The Plans I don&amp;rsquo;t clearly remember how the plan started. I can&amp;rsquo;t see how such a plan could have come into our minds except as a joke. I don&amp;rsquo;t think any of us had the faintest clue that we were capable of a such an adventure.
Wanting to see the Himalayas is something that had been driving me to plan for a tour for a long time. We might have picked Bhutan for multiple reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>